<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Intranet on Ray Shah - Digital Product Designer</title>
    <link>http://ray.thinkdesign.com/categories/intranet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Intranet on Ray Shah - Digital Product Designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ray.thinkdesign.com/categories/intranet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Framing</title>
      <link>http://ray.thinkdesign.com/post/20-lowy-framing-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ray.thinkdesign.com/post/20-lowy-framing-application/</guid>
      <description>Frame Search    The final tool with search contained within the sidebar   Lowy specialises in fine art antique and reproduction frames. They work with top galleries and museums in New York and across the world. Their clients are often very busy, and once they have aquired a work of art, they simply want a frame that fits their decor, budget and the work of art itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education Projects</title>
      <link>http://ray.thinkdesign.com/post/25-education-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ray.thinkdesign.com/post/25-education-projects/</guid>
      <description>Teacher Training Website  CUNY - City Technology   Devised a simplified user input interface for adding text, video and image data. It allows for drag-and-drop arranging/re-arranging of elements once they have been added to the page.
 User Workshops Needs Assessment Recruiting Information Arcitecture Editorial UX Informal User Testing  Living Museum The Living Museum program turns children into museum curators complete with an exhibition (typically in a school hall for one afternoon).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Work</title>
      <link>http://ray.thinkdesign.com/post/10-selected-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ray.thinkdesign.com/post/10-selected-projects/</guid>
      <description>RSS Newsfeed Site  Americanium   Cultural news aggregation site with a custom RSS module that enables periodic updates from RSS, twitter, flickr and YouTube feeds.
This product was concieved by 24 Hour Museum journalist Jon Pratty, and used guardian.com as inspiration for the content design patterns. Built on Drupal, all you do is pick interesting feeds, and the site updates itself!
 Art Direction Product Design Startup  Retail  Girogio Armani and DKNY Commissions Management System and Flash Sales Commisions management built on top of existing sales audit and employee database systems, it allows sales staff to see how much commission they have earned from any point of sale terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>